<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Changes on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/changes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Changes on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/changes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #126 - March 09, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-126/</guid>
      <description>The blockchain explorer is up The next generation of the skycoin website is online Several bug fixes: We are : We also made a significant mathematical breakthrough on the skycoin economy:     Marketing        We are: Right now we want to package:     Coin Supply Update:    The blockchain explorer is up  http://explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #124 - January 28, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-124/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-124/</guid>
      <description>Exhausting list of changes, updates and bug fixes. - Most of the wallet bugs/issues are fixed - The CLI and automated deposits and withdrawals are done, raw transactions, send to many - Continuous improvements to the wallet - Continuous improvements to the website
 CLI for meshnet daemon is working (try it) CLI for CXO daemon is in progress Designing new, next generation cross platform environment for bundling our applications and daemons  We have more academic papers coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #50 - January 13, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-50/</guid>
      <description>Changes  The unit tests are fixed The refactoring is still not done, but getting closer The json output formater for transactions is fixed/pretty printer. The way transactions are signed has been modified. Instead of signing the hash of the transaction, with the private key for the output being spent. You now sign the hash of the SHA256 sum of the output being spent with the transaction hash. This has subtle implications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #42 - November 12, 2014 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-42/</guid>
      <description>The recent attacks on Tor and incidents with Bitcoin are putting pressure on us to release.
Changes  Standardizing serialization formats. Finishing documentation. Changes to internal organization of /src/visor (which runs the blockchain). The wallet manager is moved out of visor. Visor has golang interface based upon the Obelisk Darkwallet API, then another module will run a web-server and manage your local wallets and checks for balances and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #6 - March 05, 2014 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-6/</guid>
      <description>Summary:  Fixed coin hour calculation bug. Each coin is 1 million &amp;ldquo;droplets&amp;rdquo;. Due to integer rounding error, user would not receive coinhours from output s with a balance less than one million droplets. Bug is fixed. Coinhour calculation is now based upon the block time of the previous block, not the block the transaction executed in. Unit tests in /src/coin are fixed RFC for wallet is being redone to support multiple coin wallets Design for emergency messaging system is done More developers have joined the darknet/meshnet project  Launch Checklist:  A new wire protocol is being developed for transaction propagation and block replication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #4 - March 03, 2014 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-4/</guid>
      <description>Software Update: The design of Obelisk is finalized. All the pieces come together and its a major milestone for cryptocoins. We believe that Skycoin will be the most secure, most difficult to attack non-mined cryptocoin to date.
Changes:  There is now list of things for developers to do https://github.com/skycoin/skycoin/wiki/SOFTWARE-DEVELOPERS-CLICK-HERE We introduced proof of work and difficulty re targeting to keep block production rate constant. As the network scales from 10 nodes to 100,000 we need to keep the block rate constant and prevent it from growing linearly with the number of nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>