<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Improvements on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/tags/improvements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Improvements on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/tags/improvements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #86</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-86/</guid>
      <description>There are some improvements coming up - Deprecation of the C secp256k1 library for golang version - Dependency vendoring. Means all dependencies of skycoin will be inside of the skycoin repo, for version 1.5. Improves security, makes it so that no one can insert a back door in an upstream library - golang almost has deterministic builds working. This will be exciting. If two people build the binary from source on different machines, they get SHA256 identical binaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #71</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-71/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-71/</guid>
      <description>The network has been operating for a few weeks now. It is working pretty well, but there are reliability issues over open internet that did not occur in the VPN testing environment.
The two major improvements that are needed are:  Queuing pending transactions, ensuring they are executed, blocking wallet from creating new transactions until existing transactions are executed, putting indicator in GUI to allow diagnosis of transactions that fail to propagate Major refactor of PEX (peer-exchange).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>