<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skycoin Exchange on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/skycoin-exchange/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Skycoin Exchange on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/skycoin-exchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #81 - September 10, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-81/</guid>
      <description>Exchange Overview: This is a prototype for a next-generation exchange infrastructure.
http://github.com/skycoin/skycoin-exchange
This is very rough. Your username/login is a public key. Your identifier is a hash of your public key. You sign your messages to the exchange with your public key. This will be stored in a json file locally on the client.
//send this with every request // type MsgAuth struct { Address cipher.Address Hash cipher.SHA256 //hash of the JSON message Signature cipher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #76 - July 26, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-76/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-76/</guid>
      <description>Priorities: There are many thing we want to do, but have to focus and defer a lot of things for future. Right now, there are a few things in progress.
1) Porting crypto to golang. To cross compile (to compile skycoin for windows, android, linux and OSX from a single server) all the code has to be in golang. Skycoin crypto wraps a secp256k1 library. This is being rewritten to golang but is an incredibly difficult and time consuming task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #58 - February 16, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-58/</guid>
      <description>Offline Wallets: Skycoin will have some more features for doing offline wallets or wallets on computers not connected to a network. You for instance, may generate a wallet and seed on a computer not connected to any internet. Your &amp;ldquo;cold wallet&amp;rdquo;. Then you send the coins to the first address in the code wallet. Then you load the unspent output hash by hand (typing it into the computer).
To send coins out of the code wallet, without connecting the computer to the internet, the wallet generates a transaction on the computer not connected to the network and produces a QR code you scan with a cell phone to injection that transaction into the network.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>