<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Information on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/categories/information/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Information on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/categories/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #26 - January 28, 2017</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-26/</guid>
      <description>ICO History:  The initial ICO coin price was 0.18 USD per SKY. (years ago, for developers compiling from source and people helping on project who wanted to invest) Then the coin price was pegged to bitcoin, so that investors would not be disadvantaged by the increase in the price of Bitcoin, at 2500 SKY/BTC Then people demanded we increase the price to benefit the earlier investors so we increased price to 2000 SKY/BTC  Most of the price increase from $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #25 - August 30, 2016</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-25/</guid>
      <description>People are demanding that we sell more coins before release.
At 2500 SKY/BTC, (2500 SKY per BTC)
1) Generate a skycoin address 2) Send us how many coins you want 3) We send you Bitcoin address 4) You send coins 5) We send transaction id/confirmation/output</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #24 - August 24, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-24/</guid>
      <description>IPO problems: Some people are having trouble receiving messages.
Make sure you leave bitmessage open long enough to receive the response message. To receive Bitmessage messages, you have to leave bitmessage open for about an hour. Bitmessage has to download every message on the network. If you do no leave the client open for long enough, the return message will not be received.
I am replying to the messages in under an hour, but some people are not leaving Bitmessage open long enough to receive them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #23 - July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-23/</guid>
      <description>500,000 of the Skycoin have been distributed (0.5%) . About $50,000 worth. I think we raised about $35,000 after all the coins to developers and test coins were given out. That was spent over the last six months and we have to raise more money, because contractors are screaming about being paid.
Spending so far has been very conservative and I am worried about running out of money and how much additional contractors will cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #22 - July 17, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-22/</guid>
      <description>I have spent the last week probing the Chinese firewall. Rather long post about this.
I VPN is working now. I had to tunnel through server in China that is on a business line and then tunnel out over business line to another country. I now have 8 MB/s out of country reliably. To get good speed out of the country, you need a multi-hop VPN or a MPLS installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #21 - July 08, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-21/</guid>
      <description>I tried to do bitmessage for IPO. It has had a lot of problems. Most of the users are in China and I tested it and I was getting similar problems to what I experienced with transaction propagation for Skycoin through China. Messages dont propagate sometimes and its frustrating.
I will do website, send out codes for the people on Bitmessage. That is best solution probably. Then have an exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #20 - May 02, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-20/</guid>
      <description>25% of the IPO receipts have been processed. I am this far down list now. I have not even gotten to processing the orders for the Skycoin devs yet.
I feel very bad that it is taking this long. February is almost done. Some near the top are done, so about 25% of total receipts are processed.
I generated a sequence of cold wallet addresses deterministic with skycoin, imported them into bitcoind with bash script, locked the wallet and then moved it from the cold computer to hot computer, so receipt can be verified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #19 - May 01, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-19/</guid>
      <description>I am almost done processing the IPO receipts/orders for February. So check Bitmessage.
After receipts are done, will try to code an exchange bot for Bitcoin/Skycoin convertibility. There will be a few Bitcoin per hour of liquidity injected, to keep the price floor at the IPO level and ensure convertibility between BTC/SKY.
The wallet binaries will be put onto a domain as soon as the DNS is setup. I dont like adding a dependency on DNS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #18 - April 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-18/</guid>
      <description>Processing more receipts. Everyone who sent receipts will eventually get the coins requested.
IPO Support At least one Chinese user in QQ chat has mentioned they have sent bitcoin and not received coins. The outputs are being double checked to make sure they are created, but if you have any problems, check
http://skycoin-chompyz.c9.io/blockchain/blocks?start=0&amp;amp;end=500 http://skycoin-chompyz.c9.io/outputs
If your coins appear there, but not in client then it means client is having difficult syncing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #17 - April 18, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-17/</guid>
      <description>Is the price still $0.10 / Skycoin?
 2500 Skycoin per Bitcoin. Which is about $0.10 / Skycoin. Bitcoin to USD is too volatile so just set it to that.
I am going through the bitmessage requests by hand.
I think we started getting bitmessage requests for IPO in about two months ago and are just sending out coins now. However, there have been a lot of changes and fixes since then, so steady progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #16 - April 17, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-16/</guid>
      <description>You can now do Skycoin transactions. Some people are having trouble getting peer connections however. The network will be spotty while we clean things up. We recomend updating the client to latest version every two days.
Some test coins have been sent out. - You have to find someone who has them - If you put in request on bitmessage, check your wallet and you may have test coins. These are still being sent out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #15 - April 03, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-15/</guid>
      <description>The network is running. Transactions are working. However, connecting to other clients and block replication appears to be experiencing problems.
There appears to be an issue with servers connecting peer to peer. Something may have broken in the refactor. There is an EOF error on socket read and not sure what cause is and have to check that the keep alive packet for connections is working. Clients from another application may be connecting because of the kadmelia DHT requests, but not sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #14 - April 01, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-14/</guid>
      <description>We are doing exhaustive tests and code review. There was a frustrating bug that set us back a week. 10e6 is actually 10 million in golang, not 1 million. 1 million is 1e6. This is trivial, but caused error in the coin locking system. The 100 million coins are being sent, 1 million coins to each of 100 addresses with multiparty lock system to prevent theft. There is also a time capsule lock on the private keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #13 - March 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-13/</guid>
      <description>IPO is done when its done. Fixing bugs.
 There was bug where OSX/linux treat files differently depending on whether the file name has uppercase/lower case letters that was affecting the webgui. Fixes to GUI/web wallet web wallet GUI did not report or show error on failure of send transaction There was bug where if you create a wallet, then close client and create another wallet, then close and reopen the second wallet will disappear (but only if you did this in the same day according to unix time), because the second wallet will have the same name as the first wallet because an uninitialized pseudorandom number generator was used to generate the random part of the wallet filename that is appended to the date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #12 - February 28, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-12/</guid>
      <description>The messages are being processed by hand. If instructions were too long, just:  install Bitmessage send message to BM-2cU8XJp3GPVQG75ZwMjiyzdDEa9eD4B7iM include how many Skycoin you want. At 10 cents per Skycoin. You will get receipt back. send contact information and a bitcoin address in case we need to return coins send us a Skycoin address where you want the coins  You will receive receipt  There should be some test coins in your address send bitcoin for receipt and rest of coins will show up  You should include email or bitcoin talks, qq-chat or other identity information in case we have to contact you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #11 - February 25, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-11/</guid>
      <description>IPO Status We have not started sending out confirmation receipts yet. We finished the remote server, so people can check balances.
http://skycoin-chompyz.c9.io/outputs
We also triple tested deterministic bitcoin privatekey and address generation from Skycoin. We are sure this is working now. So we can generate a unique address for each receipt in the IPO.
We will have a bitcoin wrapper over sx, when the darkwallet team makes that stable and then can store bitcoin in Skycoin wallets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #10 - February 23, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-10/</guid>
      <description>IPO START Chinese new year is done. I think everyone is back from vacation now. So we can start IPO.
IPO Instructions: Install Bitmessage:
Send message to: BM-2cU8XJp3GPVQG75ZwMjiyzdDEa9eD4B7iM
with
 { contact: &amp;quot;bitcointalks: username, github:username, email:user@domain.com&amp;quot;, bitcoin_addr: &amp;quot;bitcoin_address&amp;quot;, skycoin_addr: &amp;quot;skycoin address or seed&amp;quot;, coins_requested: &amp;quot;1000&amp;quot; }  Then you can put note or any text below that. You can put anything in the name field. You can leave it empty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #9 - January 29, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-9/</guid>
      <description>I am glad people have been able to get the client working!
Two things left, the IPO:  finishing up refactor. wallet state is now in /src/gui and visor/daemon are independent of wallet now. more work on this, but after IPO The tox bot is in python, it needs to be in golang to use some functions.  How IPO will work: There will be a bot on TOX. Install Tox, make sure it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #7 - January 18, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-7/</guid>
      <description>We are starting a mock IPO right now. To verify that everything works and make sure everyone can get it working. - Not everything is ready, so we are live coding it as we go - We distribute a bunch of fake coins, so people can do transactions, make sure everything works - So people can can learn to do transactions by hand and as tutorial on public key cryptography - Will make sure bitcoin functions work and live code trading bot - blockchain will be reset (all Skycoins coins wiped out), then can start real IPO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #8 - January 23, 2015</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-8/</guid>
      <description>We have a tox bot now. You send it your Skycoin address and it sends back a Bitcoin address. You also have to set a refund address, so that we can send coins back to you, if there is a problem.
 I am setting up system for offline generation of the bitcoin addresses on an airgapped computer, to prevent the Bitcoins from being stolen if the sever is hacked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Perspective on Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-perspective-on-monetary-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-perspective-on-monetary-policy/</guid>
      <description>What makes me the most sad, is that there are developers who bought in to Bitcoin at pennies. They made a lot of money already and very few of them gave back to the community or created something that moved the community forward. Everything is a money grab.
We have hundreds of money grab altcoins. Gimmicks. Whole cartels devoted to pump and dumps. Bitcoin is still in a penny stock and show pony, gimmick mentality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #6 - October 31, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-6/</guid>
      <description>Quote from: kingscrown on October 22, 2014, 01:08:09 AM &amp;gt;i doubt it will ever launch heh
Ya. We could have done the IPO in January. I cant remember what stopped the IPO from happening.
The IPO does not mean its done, or even that it works. It just means the coin is trading publicly. If Skycoin succeeds, it will spawn fifty clone-coins before we even have the software working.
Bitcoin took the form it did (a single large, global world internet currency) because of mining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #5 - September 16, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-5/</guid>
      <description>The IPO cannot work the way we originally intended. There is no way to cap the number of Bitcoin per person that can participate in the IPO.
Browser finger printing does not work. It cannot reliably detect which users are bots and which are not. Bot nets and even proxies still get through.
Then we were going to do IPO over Bitmessage, but with validation of Bitcoin talks username. However, there are people who have several thousands Bitcoin Talks accounts registered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #4 - August 23, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-4/</guid>
      <description>Preregistration generates a public key for you and then sends it to us through Bitmessage. You have to write down your private key, because you will need it later.
You also send - your Github account name - Bitcoin talks name - Approximate number of Bitcoin you want to put into the IPO
Pre-registration is to gauge IPO demand and control IPO so its fair. There are 100 million Skycoin. Between 2% and 10% of the total Skycoin will be sold in the IPO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on the Origin of Skycoin</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/musings-on-the-origin-of-skycoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/musings-on-the-origin-of-skycoin/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin development started two years after Bitcoin was released. The Skycoin Project is almost as old as Litecoin. I cant even remember if Bitcoin had hit a dollar yet or if there were even exchanges when project started.
The first version was in python and was completely working. Then codebase was moved to C++, then moved to Golang. So it has already gone through three language changes. The longest working Skycoin blockchain was running for four months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #3 - August 22, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-udpate-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-udpate-3/</guid>
      <description>IPO pre-registration begins in a few hours. Trying to get binaries compiled and making sure this bitmessage library works.
Pre-registration will last two weeks. Until the 6th of September. Pre-registration will be required for the IPO.
During pre-registration, you run a program (or from source), it generates a private key/public key pair and sends it over Bitmessage. Then another server will send back response confirming of registration in the IPO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Question Regarding Latency and Privacy of the Meshnet</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/question-regarding-latency-and-privacy-of-the-meshnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/question-regarding-latency-and-privacy-of-the-meshnet/</guid>
      <description>Quote from: CraigM on August 09, 2014, 07:20:24 AM
 The meshnet is intended to be a nice privacy tool with benefits comparable to tor, but lower latency correct?
The meshnet is intended to allow funding nodes via micropayments in skycoin to cover bandwidth costs correct? Doesn&amp;rsquo;t this leave force all node operators to record detailed and published logs (on their personal block chains) describing all the transactions which inherently correspond to everyone who send data through their node?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Further Clarification of Obelisk</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/further-clarification-of-obelisk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/further-clarification-of-obelisk/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin has a blockchain. The blockchain is in skycoin/src/coin. That parses the blocks and deals with unspent outputs and transactions.
Skywire is the daemon and has a &amp;ldquo;service architecture&amp;rdquo;. It can run services, such as blockchain syncing service and other things. The meshnet is currently being implemented as a service on top of Skywire (although this may need to change).
The consensus mechanism is outside of the blockchain. Obelisk nodes (probably will be implemented as a Skywire service) have a blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Well Does the Meshnet Work?</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/how-well-does-the-meshnet-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/how-well-does-the-meshnet-work/</guid>
      <description>Quote from: Korean on September 26, 2014, 05:45:00 AM &amp;gt;How well does the Meshnet work right now? &amp;gt;Can it get pass the great firewall of China? &amp;gt;Is there a standard hardware that you recommend?
Yes. It was designed explicitly to defeat existing state-full packet inspection hardware. This includes the great firewall.
There is no fixed port, no protocol headers. There is not a single byte of plain text traffic in wire protocol, which can be used for identification of the protocol type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #2 - June 19, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update-2/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin will have a rolling IPO. The IPO will be very small, then a small number of coins will be released on to an exchange each day. If the price decreases, the number of newly issued coins will be decreased to stabilize price. If the price goes too low, the developers will begin buying back coins.
The majority of distribution will go to developers, people involved in marketing and people buying and operating a mesh network nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quorum Proof of Stake</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/quorum-proof-of-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/quorum-proof-of-stake/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: iruu on May 18, 2014, 10:40:39 AM &amp;gt;A decentralized distributed consensus currency, so to speak. At least aiming to be decentralized. &amp;gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really get the why. Why not some variation of proof of stake? For example a version where one stake equals one virtual node. No need for trust when there&amp;rsquo;s financial interest.
Yes. We actually have two layers of proof-of-stake. There is the blockchain consensus, then within the blockchain we have coinhours, which are burned as fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Update #1 - May 15, 2014</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-update/</guid>
      <description>What we will probably do, is have a pre-IPO &amp;ldquo;order commitment&amp;rdquo;. Users will Bitcoin account histories and/or Github accounts and project contributors will be allowed to commit to IPO, up to percentage of the IPO. Participation will be capped at 5 BTC and the cap will go down as the pool gets depleted.
Then the people who have been following project for a while, will get a guaranteed commitment to IPO, without worrying about timing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Economic Policy</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-economic-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-economic-policy/</guid>
      <description>We have been talking to a large Bitcoin market marker about how we can prevent a repeat of the Auroacoin crash and deter speculators.
We have a data guy doing models.
This is the linear scale Bitcoin price over time
This is log scale Bitcoin price, with regression line. When Bitcoin is over the line its over priced, when its below the line its underpriced.
This is the total number of subscribers in /r/bitcoin This is the daily growth rate of subscribers in /r/bitcoin .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clarification on the Personal Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/clarification-on-the-personal-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/clarification-on-the-personal-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: FrictionlessCoin on May 06, 2014, 01:08:09 PM &amp;gt;I still however am have trouble understanding how the protocol works and this notion of &amp;lsquo;personal blockchains&amp;rsquo;. Can you point me to the documentation that describes this better?
For a person blockchain, you generate a public key. To be valid you have to sign each block with your private key.
The details of the replication protocol are in the first two pages of the Aether whitepaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin is a Next Generation Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-next-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/skycoin-next-generation/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: -Greed- on May 05, 2014, 04:25:46 PM &amp;gt;+1 for skycoin being truly 2nd-gen coin. Bitcoin and all its forks are first-gen IMO.
Some of the things we are laying the foundations for are third gen. A working, usable coin, with a clean code base and good security, no mining, no 51% attack and a reason to use the coin is just second gen.
Digital contracts, communication and identity infrastructure lay the foundation for the third gen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Skycoin to Ripple</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/comparing-skycoin-to-ripple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/comparing-skycoin-to-ripple/</guid>
      <description>In Ripple you have a bunch of node. If a peer rejects a transaction, then to achieve consensus, the connection&amp;rsquo;s peers will drop the transaction and the rejection of the transaction propagates through the network. That means that a single bad node can freeze the assets in a particular address.
Ripple is must more vulnerable to government influence and control than Bitcoin, because control of the network is centralized in financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to Where We Think Bitcoin Should Be</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: JFK01 on April 23, 2014, 01:54:50 PM
 I guess that Skycoin just want to test the water first. There is nothing wrong with that. They are engineers and want to do testing for everything. They have been very cautious for the development as well. This is something they are good at. Just do what you are good at. This project is a long shot.
 If you look at the top coins, Peer Coin, Ripple, Bitcoin, Nxt, Litecoin, its clear that most coins with a fundamental innovation on Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s security model have done very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Meaning of Aether</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/the-meaning-of-ather/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/the-meaning-of-ather/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: Tobo on May 04, 2014, 02:11:12 PM &amp;gt;I noticed that you previously used the name of ether which was used by Ethereum. Now you changed it to aether which has been used by some other people at this forum. Why did you like these two names so much?
Ether permutes space. Then we found out ether is alcohol that people snuff to get high and aether is the mystical substance that permutes space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Security Measures</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/reasons-for-ipo-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/reasons-for-ipo-structure/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: CryptoFinanceUK on April 18, 2014, 04:20:29 PM
Quote from: *skycoin* on April 18, 2014, 01:05:39 PM 1 million coins (1%) will be sold for 50k in Bitcoin.   So from an investors point of view, we&amp;rsquo;d need to believe in a $5m valuation at launch. That&amp;rsquo;s almost top ten territory, market cap wise.
What&amp;rsquo;s the plan for distributing the remaining 99%?
 Response: Maidsafe is raising 6 million dollars at 120 million dollar valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Skycoin Decentralized?</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/is-skycoin-decentralized/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/is-skycoin-decentralized/</guid>
      <description>To prototype Skycoin, we used a mix of centralized and decentralized components for prototyping. We prototyped Skycoin and the emphasis was getting each component working. Over time the centralized components have been replaced by fully decentralized components. Skycoin will be fully independent of any developer run servers and infrastructure by the time Obelisk is finished.
Right now - the ledger is decentralized, everyone has a copy of the transaction ledger - transactions are decentralized and the transaction relay is peer to peer - blockchain consensus requires Obelisk for full decentralization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Security Measures</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-security-measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-security-measures/</guid>
      <description>We made the final changes to the deterministic wallet generation. Final security preparations for the IPO are beginning.
Recently, hackers have been targeting coin IPOs for attack. We are generating the private keys for the IPO addresses offline, from a computer that has not been connected to the internet and then moving the addresses via USB drive in 1 million coin batches.
We are taking measures to proxy the server authorizing the IPO transactions to prevent identification of the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Blockchain Transactions:</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/cross-blockchain-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/cross-blockchain-transactions/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: CraigM on April 15, 2014, 07:11:29 AM &amp;gt;It seem like most of these proposed features (enforceable contracts, distributed trust-less exchanges, reputation systems etc) all come from the core feature of cross chain transactions. Cross chain transactions allow adding other currencies/goods to the economy that can be securely exchanged. This is a very powerful feature which solves tons of problems including the scalability ones (you can shard the currency if the distributed consensus becomes too expensive, or even add ultra low transaction cost centralized sub-currencies that can be converted back to any other currency)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oblelisk Explained</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/oblelisk-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/oblelisk-explained/</guid>
      <description>What is Obelisk? Obelisk is what makes Skycoin, Bitcoin 2.0. Obelisk is a sustainable alternative to proof-of-work. Obelisk is a system that replaces proof of work for blockchain consensus and eliminates the possibility of a 51% attack.
Obelisk was inspired by academic research into adversarial distributed time-stamping and algorithms such as Ben-Or&amp;rsquo;s, Paxos, and the Castro-Liskov PBFT algorithm. Obelisk is a new solution to the Byzantine Generals problem which offers strong mathematical security guarantees, even when the majority of nodes are hostile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Marketing and Speculation</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/thoughts-on-marketing-and-speculation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/thoughts-on-marketing-and-speculation/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on Marketing and Speculation: Skycoin marketing is highly targeted at influence groups and communities who need to know about Skycoin. The objective of Skycoin marketing is to build out the community and build awareness. Skycoin is not doing broad marketing aimed at public to &amp;ldquo;pump&amp;rdquo; prices to unsustainable levels. Skycoin will not be paying Lady Gaga to make a Skycoin music video.
Marketing tactics designed to cause bubbles and bursts are great for speculators, day trading and people organizing the pumps, but conflict with Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s objective of low volatility and stable price levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwoStep: Post Quantum Secure Transactions</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/twostep--post-quantum-secure-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/twostep--post-quantum-secure-transactions/</guid>
      <description>TwoStep: Post Quantum Secure Transactions Future advances in mathematics may render Bitcoin insecure. This is a draft protocol for securing cryptocoin transactions against future advances in mathematics or computing which render discrete logarithm based public key cryptography insecure.
TwoStep is part of QuantumEclipse, a suite of next-gen cryptocoin protocols developed under OP Darknet Plan for the Skycoin Project.
This protocol is - simple - adaptable to Bitcoin - lower overhead than Lamport Signatures - works with SHA256 preimages equally as well as Secp256k1 signatures - not dependent on the security of discrete logarithm based public key cryptography</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Obelisk: Distributed Consensus </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/overview-of-obelisk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/overview-of-obelisk/</guid>
      <description>Overview of Obelisk: Distributed Consensus In Obelisk, each person runs their own Obelisk nodes. Each node has a set of trust relationships with other nodes. Each node has a list of servers it &amp;ldquo;trusts&amp;rdquo;. A new node can be initialized by randomly choosing a few dozen existing nodes to trust, with only two or three of the nodes being nodes run by trusted institutions or persons.
Servers publish &amp;ldquo;blocks&amp;rdquo; every 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>