<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bugs on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/bugs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bugs on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/bugs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #131</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-131/</guid>
      <description>Bug Fix: We found a bug last night, where the node goes into infinite loop when trying to create a new block and transactions on network stopped.
The node was assembling 5 transactions into a block, then failing because two transaction tried to spend the same output. Then failing and waiting a few seconds and then trying again with same result.
The code is now enabled to take the list of pending transactions and add random transactions from the list, one at a time, discarding a transactions which if added to the block, would make the block unexecutable against the current unspent output set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #82</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-82/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-82/</guid>
      <description>There is a major and very severe bug. I am upset that no one found this or brought it up earlier.
For some reason, for some clients under some networking conditions the blockchain is not downloading until it reaches the head block. On LAN and running multiple instances on the same machine, the blockchain always synchronizes between all the clients in testing. In the real world, behind VPN, with latency, and servers in multiple countries the blockchain is not always syncing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #69</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-69/</guid>
      <description>There was a &amp;ldquo;disappearing coins&amp;rdquo; bug on windows.  You download all ~120 blocks, you see 100 coins You close client, there is not sig signal for clear program exit triggered on windows, so you lose all the blocks (they are not saved to disc, like they are on exit, on linux) You open client and the coins are &amp;ldquo;missing&amp;rdquo;, until you redownload the blockchain to current head  So coins were still there and appears to just be bug with blockchain not being saved to disc on exit on windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #68</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-68/</guid>
      <description>New Bugs:  If you try to send and the send fails because of insufficient coins, it did not give a popup and only printed error in terminal. That is fixed now. There was a bug discovered yesterday, where you can do multiple transactions from the same inputs (only one of the transactions will succeed). So if you do two sends form same wallet and transaction propagation is not successful, then some of the transactions wont go through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #11</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-11/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Most of the work in last week has been in the new wire protocol repo. Should be on github soon.
Skycoin License: The license will be a standard open source license. Current license is:  You can distribute code for non-commercial use You can modify code for non-commercial use You agree to copyright assignment under the to be determined open source license You grant perpetual license to use, distribute and modify any contributed code  We might have terms like &amp;ldquo;no forking coin without permission for 24 months after date X&amp;rdquo; and then license is MIT or GNU after that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>