<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Autonomous Corporations on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/digital-autonomous-corporations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Autonomous Corporations on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/digital-autonomous-corporations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #33</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-33/</guid>
      <description>Skywire Repo Moved: The Skywire repository has been merged into the main Skycoin repository. Still being integrated to replace visor and daemon.
Skycoin Cryptography Standard Library All the cryptography, hashing and address operations have been moved into github.com/skycoin/skycoin/src/cipher
https://github.com/skycoin/skycoin/tree/master/src/cipher
The library is in progress. It will be common core for addresses, hashing and cryptography across Skycoin, distributed applications and wallets.
The new library will support:  secp256k1 public and private key generation secp256k1 signature, signature verification and chksig operations Secure deterministic wallet generation operator (secp256k1 curve right multiplication with SHA256 hashing) Secure random number generation (mixes entropy from multiple sources on top of system secure random number generator) SHA256 merkle tree implementation for radix 2 and 16 ECDH (Elliptic curve Diffie-Hellman) deniable encryption with secp256k1 and ChaCha20 SHA256, Ripmd160, ChaCha20 implementation Base58 encoding for Skycoin and Bitcoin Addresses May in future specify binary wallet file format for key storage  Project Management: Dependency Difficulties Golang is a new language and dependency management is still difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>