<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skywire on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/skywire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Skywire on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/skywire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #107</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-107/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-107/</guid>
      <description>The Skycoin blockchain history JSON API is done: The first version of the Skycoin block storage library is done: The Skycoin CLI and WebRPC interface API is in progress: The first version of Skywire interface is done. It is being integrated with the JSON API now. You will have a number of &amp;ldquo;Nodes&amp;rdquo; that you control (your &amp;ldquo;personal cloud&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;personal botnet&amp;rdquo; really) For instance, for dropbox type storage This is actually a distributed multi-agent system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #75</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-75/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-75/</guid>
      <description>The coin is done. We are working on networking. There are three different groups working independently on that and its not on github yet.
The coin needs:  Database for storing blocks Database for history gui improvements Misc improvements (the blockchain does not save on windows when closing)  We have to move on to next part to keep schedule. Then new people can work on coin improvements. The improvements are marginal at this stage and could take up almost all the project resources if we only focused on that at this stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #72</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-72/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-72/</guid>
      <description>Summary: The coin is basicly done. Other people can come in and polish up the hundreds of other things now. There are two developers working on front end and api, so will speed it along. Nothing else that is absolutely critical and not incremental needs to be done. There are still hundreds of small changes, improvements, refactoring to be done but it can be ignored for now.
After the coin distribution receipts are done, then schedule is cleared for consensus implementation and meshnet/darknet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #44</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-44/</guid>
      <description>This is over view of current development status and priorities
Consensus Consensus is being worked on. The earlier algorithms are being implemented, bench-marked. Then testing them against the newer algorithms, so we have comparison. This is currently in python. Will be moved to golang and integrated as soon as its ready.
This is not required for the distribution , because we can use central signing key until decentralized consensus is implemented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #34</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-34/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Massive changes. Everything is now in one repository. https://github.com/skycoin/skycoin
Changes skycoin/src/coin is the blockchain parser library skycoin/src/cipher is the Skycoin Standard Crytographic library skycoin/src/aether is the distributed application services library skycoin/src/skywire is the Skycoin Meshnet/Darknet switch skycoin/src/gui is the HTML local web wallet and infrastructure
 All of the cryptographic and hashing functions have been moved into a common library, that can be imported and used across different applications Skywire is now the meshnet/darknet instead of the services daemon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #33</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-33/</guid>
      <description>Skywire Repo Moved: The Skywire repository has been merged into the main Skycoin repository. Still being integrated to replace visor and daemon.
Skycoin Cryptography Standard Library All the cryptography, hashing and address operations have been moved into github.com/skycoin/skycoin/src/cipher
https://github.com/skycoin/skycoin/tree/master/src/cipher
The library is in progress. It will be common core for addresses, hashing and cryptography across Skycoin, distributed applications and wallets.
The new library will support:  secp256k1 public and private key generation secp256k1 signature, signature verification and chksig operations Secure deterministic wallet generation operator (secp256k1 curve right multiplication with SHA256 hashing) Secure random number generation (mixes entropy from multiple sources on top of system secure random number generator) SHA256 merkle tree implementation for radix 2 and 16 ECDH (Elliptic curve Diffie-Hellman) deniable encryption with secp256k1 and ChaCha20 SHA256, Ripmd160, ChaCha20 implementation Base58 encoding for Skycoin and Bitcoin Addresses May in future specify binary wallet file format for key storage  Project Management: Dependency Difficulties Golang is a new language and dependency management is still difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #31</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-31/</guid>
      <description>Cryptography Upgrades: We are getting a function for encrypting blocks of data with ECCDH. There will be simple function that takes a public key and encrypts to binary and a simple function that takes the recipients private key for decryption from bytes.
Encryption Format: struct EncryptedMessage { Pubkey Pubkey //ephemeral pubkey Q Data []byte //padded to 4096 bytes, length prefix and 32 bit checksum }  Their pubkey is P, your ephemeral pubkey is Q.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #28</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-28/</guid>
      <description>Skywire Meshnet The design is amazing. Skywire darknet router may be able to replace BGP and existing corporate VPN solutions. Its reverse comparable with IPv6 (IPv6 can be embedded over Skywire). Its very simple.
I dont want to talk much about this. Just have to finish implementation and get source code out there.
Skycoin Application Framework Extremely exciting. We have compiler for compiling Golang down to Javascript.
https://github.com/gopherjs/gopherjs
 Aether apps will be in Golang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #23</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-23/</guid>
      <description>White paper The Skycoin meshnet white paper is done: Skywire*
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1_rPNMTokwmBPFel1pZfLbTtTkooSWtGKrTLB3RbXIrI
We thought the new developers could learn golang in two days and its taking a bit longer, especially with getting up to date on the code base and what needs to be done and why its structured the way it is. Working on better system for coordinating the work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #18</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-18/</guid>
      <description>Skywire Everything was working in January; launch has been delayed because of refactoring. We are exhausted because of coding coin. Everyone wants to get coin over with and get meshnet working. We can get a lot of press on reddit by delivering the meshnet. People are rioting because of Comcast/net neutrality right now.
Everyone is ready to deploy nodes in their city, setup local meetings, develop hardware and coordinate deployment across North America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #11</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-11/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Most of the work in last week has been in the new wire protocol repo. Should be on github soon.
Skycoin License: The license will be a standard open source license. Current license is:  You can distribute code for non-commercial use You can modify code for non-commercial use You agree to copyright assignment under the to be determined open source license You grant perpetual license to use, distribute and modify any contributed code  We might have terms like &amp;ldquo;no forking coin without permission for 24 months after date X&amp;rdquo; and then license is MIT or GNU after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #10</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-10/</guid>
      <description>Summary: The new wire protocol is more work than expected. Instead of delaying launch by two weeks, to address these issues I am hacking together something that will get the network running.
Multiple software components need to be be refactored:  Daemon needs to be extended to support multiple connection pools with independent peer exchange and using a common listening socket gnet needs to be modified to support an introduction packet gnet packet handling callbacks need to be embedded in the gnet object instead of globals, to allow multiple gnet instances in the same application daemon DHT functionality for peer bootstrap needs to be abstracted to allow for retrieving bootstrap peers for multiple hashes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>