<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fixes on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/fixes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fixes on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/fixes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #131 - May 16, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-131/</guid>
      <description>Bug Fix: We found a bug last night, where the node goes into infinite loop when trying to create a new block and transactions on network stopped.
The node was assembling 5 transactions into a block, then failing because two transaction tried to spend the same output. Then failing and waiting a few seconds and then trying again with same result.
The code is now enabled to take the list of pending transactions and add random transactions from the list, one at a time, discarding a transactions which if added to the block, would make the block unexecutable against the current unspent output set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #129 - April 26, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-129/</guid>
      <description>This edge cases happens: To fix this edge case we This should also fix the unrelated bug where: This bug was resolved by:     Exponential Backoff with Zero Peers Bug Peer Exchange Bug    We are doing misc quality control and major bug fixes now
We fixed a few bugs and path directory issues for the windows non-electron build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #126 - March 09, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-126/</guid>
      <description>The blockchain explorer is up The next generation of the skycoin website is online Several bug fixes: We are : We also made a significant mathematical breakthrough on the skycoin economy:     Marketing        We are: Right now we want to package:     Coin Supply Update:    The blockchain explorer is up  http://explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #124 - January 28, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-124/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-124/</guid>
      <description>Exhausting list of changes, updates and bug fixes. - Most of the wallet bugs/issues are fixed - The CLI and automated deposits and withdrawals are done, raw transactions, send to many - Continuous improvements to the wallet - Continuous improvements to the website
 CLI for meshnet daemon is working (try it) CLI for CXO daemon is in progress Designing new, next generation cross platform environment for bundling our applications and daemons  We have more academic papers coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #123 - January 27, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-123/</guid>
      <description>We fixed eighty wallet bugs. Look at commits on github.
The CLI is substantially upgraded and automated deposits and withdrawals are working now. Hundreds of changes and improves to the Skycoin CLI interface.
We upgraded to latest version of electron and the copy/paste issues are fixed.
32 bit windows builds should be ready in next release.
We are creating installers for windows and OSX, so that you can install skycoin like a native application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #89 - December 12, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-89/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-89/</guid>
      <description>Fixes: Fixed dozens of bugs with the crypto library port.
The sipa and gocoin libsecp256k1 implementation differ slightly and output different public keys for the same private key for some inputs (every few thousand keys).
Slightly different public keys are outputted for the same secret key.
seckey = 8ba2269ad9d5090c891043dcbda618802d50bbfd7aa548173a9ecb5d2107ffbc pubkey1 = 02ec9b470f72b4a28d1ae507d7c8ddfa5c5385db96e905400175093e48ef5ace0d pubkey2 = 02ec9b470f72b4a28d1ae507d7c8ddfa5c5385db96e905800175093e48ef5ace0d
seckey = e329e5d4f6224566c3464dbe16bdae499566504d7cbca6b77274f835e4838c7e pubkey1 = 022c3166ffaed91846653d0179b2daf467d0a736e94ca1c0020cd165881aeee572 pubkey2 = 022c3166ffaed91846653d0179b2daf467d0a736e94ca200020cd165881aeee572
seckey = 27fa25141c11169208c822e8bb6a1dcd3f991dfd20f393a184498434695e0e14 pubkey1 = 03bd957a507e3f7fdeeb7487613acfbd931a600f9d0806000042fc54bc548a2e05 pubkey2 = 03bd957a507e3f7fdeeb7487613acfbd931a600f9d0806400042fc54bc548a2e05</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #83 - September 12, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-83/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-83/</guid>
      <description>I fixed the bug! The blockchain now downloads in under 2 seconds!
I actually have no idea why the blockchain was downloading at all. After receiving new blocks, it was not downloading more blocks until the next block announcement. Now after receiving new blocks, it asks for more blocks.
EVERYONE MUST UPDATE THE CLIENT. GIT PULL I made change, so that clients can control the number of blocks in each request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #70 - April 20, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-70/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-70/</guid>
      <description>Bug Fixes: Networking Yesterday, as soon as soon people started connecting to network, we found out how unreliable the internet is. People had difficulty connecting to servers. The majority of client did not have open ports so could not accept incoming connections. People had to wait hours for connections and then transactions were not propagating for some users, depending on country.
I disabled DHT and PEX and just hardcoded list of servers and then clients connected within half a second and it worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #67 - April 17, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-67/</guid>
      <description>Fixed a lot of bugs.
The top levels, the gui and json are not as polished as lower levels (blockchain/crypto). I have not even looked at some of this code and discovering new things. There were things implemented, I didnt know we had working and things that needed to be cleaned up.
 There was a coinhour calculate bug that prevented transactions in strange cases. I hardcoded coinhour fee for transactions to 1, to get it working, but then after receiving coins, some people were unable to send them out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #61 - March 12, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-61/</guid>
      <description>Summary Two days were spent fixing a bug with where &amp;ldquo;req.ParseMultipartForm()&amp;rdquo; needed to be called instead of &amp;ldquo;req.ParseForm()&amp;rdquo; because URL get/post parameters were not showing up correctly in logs. The url was working in unit tests, but was broken in wallet gui and still trying to determine reason. As soon as this is fixed, will begin sending out test coins.
Then the transaction &amp;ldquo;readable&amp;rdquo; for human readable transaction format is broken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #51 - January 20, 2015 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-51/</guid>
      <description>We had a productive day yesterday. Some people were able to get builds working immediately. Other people had problems with golang and path issues we are working through.
We launched the blockchain after a few hours of work. Fixed half a dozen bugs.  Several changes to build script Updated gvm curl build flags Updated to go1.4 Fixed bug with genesis block timestamp not accepting configuration setting Documentation here: https://piratepad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #48 - December 25, 2014 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-48/</guid>
      <description>The new wallet API will separate out checking balances, getting unspent outputs and injection transactions.     Hardware Wallet    I pushed a few fixes. The wallet is still buggy but looks great.
Refactoring is not as easy as I would like. If you split two modules in golang, that have minor depedencies, it will not compile because of circular dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #36 - July 29, 2014 </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-36/</guid>
      <description>Summary: We are exhausted. We just finished 4th cryptography audit. Some minor issues were found and fixed. All the issue involved impossible conditions, but are fixed anyways.
Cryptography Audit/Changes: Fixed:  Someone with a private key from a deterministic wallet who is able to do a SHA256 preimage attack was able to derive all subsequent keys in deterministic wallet (but not the keys for addresses preceding). SHA256 preimage attacks are currently impossible but may become an issue in thirty years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>