<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Update on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Update on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #127</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-127/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin is finally getting an order book. This took too long. - next exchange upgrade/rewrite skycoin will float against bitcoin
The blog is going to be ready tomorrow and we will start migrating content.
We are going to announce several partnerships with large mainstream institutions, so have to cleanup a bunch of stuff and will migrate anything relevant to blog.
We will put a lot of content on the blog and things we have not revealed yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #115</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-115/</guid>
      <description>90 commits.  The Command Line Interface is done. The first version of the WebRPC interface is in the repo  Almost done with check box for floating on exchange.
The CLI in next push will have - Adding private key to wallet by private key hex - Transactions for spending outputs held by a single address by private key - Working send</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #108</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-108/</guid>
      <description>We want to have everything done for the coin in three weeks:  The three white papers The website The CLI and WebRPC listing The blockchain explorer interface in the wallet Exchange listing Full consensus implementation Easy way for people to buy and sell coins  The critical things are:  Website CLI / WebRPC Block chain explorer in wallet  Everyone agrees that getting listed and completion of the coin is a higher priority than finishing the apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #100</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-100/</guid>
      <description>Some of the developers had problem with management style and were confused about what needed to be done. Now I am trying - I assigned one thing to each developer - I narrowed the task down to be very simple and self contained - There is a group to recruit developers and staff developers to tasks now
We are trying to split everything up, into small manageable tasks.
Now they are saying everything will take two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #78</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-79/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-79/</guid>
      <description>I have switched the peer list to json instead of csv and am merging in the blacklist and peer lists.
The new peer list format looks like.
This is first step to adding new fields to the peer list state and renabling PEX (peer-exchange). Fake peers were being spammed when we were using DHT for peer-discovery. This meant it could take up to two minutes to find a valid peer and begin downloading the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #78</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-78/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-78/</guid>
      <description>Golang 1.5 has support for android and iPhone now. - https://blog.golang.org/go1.5
This means can do mobile wallet soon or get Skycoin to compile for arm at least.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #64</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-64/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-64/</guid>
      <description>IPFS Demo: This is IPFS. This is the successor to Bitorrent.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8CMxDNuuAiQ
Skycoin Merkle-dag system is based upon this.  A directory is a list of nodes. The id of the node is the hash of its serialization Each node is either a folder or a file. The contents of files are hashes The owner signs the root hash with their private key The node metadata and files are replicated peer-to-peer The directory is referenced by a  Users can update the files after they upload them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #63</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-63/</guid>
      <description>If you know your wallet seed, you will be fine. You can open up the wallets with text editor and grab the seed. As long as you have this value, your wallet can never be lost. You can also just copy and paste the wallet directory.
Eventually, I want to change the wallet deterministic generation function to SHA3/Keccak sponge function based instead of SHA256, but it is too late for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #52</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-52/</guid>
      <description>This requires moving : Then there are several other improvements that can be done:        Here is todo list. Help appreciated. https://piratepad.ca/p/skycoin_todo
We will try to write more todo lists.
There is a major problem. All of the coins are in the genesis address and I cannot spend them for an unknown reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #37</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/development-updates/development-update-37/</guid>
      <description>Organizational Update: The original plan was to put it on Aether, however it will be months before that is working. The networking refactor was a major headache, was a massive amount of work and ended up going nowhere, but took four months. The upside is that we have a very clear architecture now.
The current plan, is that the ICO prospectus is being written. It is about 200 pages. It lays out each component in the Skycoin project, in the details required for implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>