<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speculation on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/speculation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speculation on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/speculation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing an IPO Date</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/choosing-an-ipo-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/choosing-an-ipo-date/</guid>
      <description>Choosing an IPO Date: There are two options.
 We set a date and the IPO occurs on that date, whether coin is ready or not. We wait until coin is ready (keeps getting pushed back) and announce IPO after its ready.  The coin launch and IPO will definitely occur before Obelisk is implemented, which may take through July.
Does Febuary 24th, noon GMT time for IPO sound good?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Marketing and Speculation</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/thoughts-on-marketing-and-speculation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/thoughts-on-marketing-and-speculation/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on Marketing and Speculation: Skycoin marketing is highly targeted at influence groups and communities who need to know about Skycoin. The objective of Skycoin marketing is to build out the community and build awareness. Skycoin is not doing broad marketing aimed at public to &amp;ldquo;pump&amp;rdquo; prices to unsustainable levels. Skycoin will not be paying Lady Gaga to make a Skycoin music video.
Marketing tactics designed to cause bubbles and bursts are great for speculators, day trading and people organizing the pumps, but conflict with Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s objective of low volatility and stable price levels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>