<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TwoStep: Post Quantum Secure Transactions</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/twostep--post-quantum-secure-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/twostep--post-quantum-secure-transactions/</guid>
      <description>TwoStep: Post Quantum Secure Transactions Future advances in mathematics may render Bitcoin insecure. This is a draft protocol for securing cryptocoin transactions against future advances in mathematics or computing which render discrete logarithm based public key cryptography insecure.
TwoStep is part of QuantumEclipse, a suite of next-gen cryptocoin protocols developed under OP Darknet Plan for the Skycoin Project.
This protocol is - simple - adaptable to Bitcoin - lower overhead than Lamport Signatures - works with SHA256 preimages equally as well as Secp256k1 signatures - not dependent on the security of discrete logarithm based public key cryptography</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Obelisk: Distributed Consensus </title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/overview-of-obelisk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/overview-of-obelisk/</guid>
      <description>Overview of Obelisk: Distributed Consensus In Obelisk, each person runs their own Obelisk nodes. Each node has a set of trust relationships with other nodes. Each node has a list of servers it &amp;ldquo;trusts&amp;rdquo;. A new node can be initialized by randomly choosing a few dozen existing nodes to trust, with only two or three of the nodes being nodes run by trusted institutions or persons.
Servers publish &amp;ldquo;blocks&amp;rdquo; every 5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>