<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Skycoin Updates</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Skycoin Updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #9</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-9/</guid>
      <description>Summary  Wire protocol almost done Deterministic wallets RPC almost done (in branch) Fixing wallet GUI to match new RPC Windows, OSX and linux build scripts are done  We are working towards a launch where the coin is trading as soon as possible. After launch, there is still work to do.
Skycoin Checkpoint System This is overview of the Skycoin checkpoint system. The checkpoint system addresses the exponential growth of the blockchain, by keeping the data required to run a full client to less than one gigabyte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update #3</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog/development-updates/development-update-3/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Skycoin now has bullet proof security. - There are very strict rules in place for transaction propagation and signature verification. - Bitcoin is only able to fix 6 of the 8 transaction malleability problems. Skycoin has 0 transaction malleability and 0 signature malleability bugs. - Most of the code base is unit tested. There are three lines of tests for every line of code. - we fixed bug in the struct encoder and the change broke compatibility with packets from earlier versions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>