<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ipo on Skycoin Project Material</title>
    <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/ipo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ipo on Skycoin Project Material</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.skycoin.net/tags/ipo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Security Measures</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/reasons-for-ipo-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/reasons-for-ipo-structure/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: CryptoFinanceUK on April 18, 2014, 04:20:29 PM
Quote from: *skycoin* on April 18, 2014, 01:05:39 PM 1 million coins (1%) will be sold for 50k in Bitcoin.   So from an investors point of view, we&amp;rsquo;d need to believe in a $5m valuation at launch. That&amp;rsquo;s almost top ten territory, market cap wise.
What&amp;rsquo;s the plan for distributing the remaining 99%?
 Response: Maidsafe is raising 6 million dollars at 120 million dollar valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPO Security Measures</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-security-measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/ipo-security-measures/</guid>
      <description>We made the final changes to the deterministic wallet generation. Final security preparations for the IPO are beginning.
Recently, hackers have been targeting coin IPOs for attack. We are generating the private keys for the IPO addresses offline, from a computer that has not been connected to the internet and then moving the addresses via USB drive in 1 million coin batches.
We are taking measures to proxy the server authorizing the IPO transactions to prevent identification of the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing an IPO Date</title>
      <link>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/choosing-an-ipo-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.skycoin.net/blog-posts/choosing-an-ipo-date/</guid>
      <description>Choosing an IPO Date: There are two options.
 We set a date and the IPO occurs on that date, whether coin is ready or not. We wait until coin is ready (keeps getting pushed back) and announce IPO after its ready.  The coin launch and IPO will definitely occur before Obelisk is implemented, which may take through July.
Does Febuary 24th, noon GMT time for IPO sound good?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>